{
    "id": "7758f4246ee2492ea9d34acdab49ed96",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………….. she was a foreigner made it difficult for her to get a job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "That",
                "The fact that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fcc359484e344229bdefd283968c213f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will come with you …………………. your wife doesn’t mind.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "providing that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ffa19a52c5c041e0ba88674cc57b4fb1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am very …………………… for all your help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "thankful",
                "grateful",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "46960ed98dd7428bb3315c6a452d368b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is thinking ………………….. her job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to quit",
                "of quitting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fd6f92d1c596479694949a4c26ec6acb"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………. a terrorist.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "thought",
                "was thought to be"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1bdad3c947a24352b76bbd59a0611d7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She spent ………………… browsing through the catalogue.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ten happy minutes",
                "happy ten minutes",
                "a happy ten minutes"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "763a680dacfb4d728ea925b4dba27a2a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am very …………………. in the lesson.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "interesting",
                "interested"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e7a290bb75514185ab8c3426e53ba369"
        },
        {
            "question": "I mean ………………….. what is going on.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to find out",
                "finding out"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "893f5ee66f9e47b5b2751ff0dc564367"
        },
        {
            "question": "You should always check the oil before ………………….. the car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "starting",
                "to start"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c74c937ba3f5438cac2936adc047c961"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am tired ………………… to this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to listen",
                "of listening"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a9a77c26a61848b1b26fc5cb41ca3572"
        }
    ]
}